[theme music playing]
[Diego] I still believe
there's hope for this town.
No matter what you do,
you can't change their lives.
Not as long as this family is in power.
[Ivy] I feel nothing but pain,
anger, and fury.
I promise you and Dad,
I'll avenge your deaths.
[screaming]
[Diego] Their project here
will push through.
They got more funds from
the huge amount Ivy Aguas invested.
[woman] The congressman's statue
was destroyed last night.
[Julio] Monitor who goes
in and out of town.
Do a background check on all of them.
-[Emilia] Does this include, Ivy?
-Especially Ivy.
[Julio] These things started
the moment she came here.
[Emilia] I'll uncover her deepest secrets.
Governor, now that someone's openly
going against you, it's troubling.
I'm starting to reconsider my investment.
[Julio] We have to fix this.
We need that woman and her money.
Talk to Arnaldo.
He can handle this better than you.
[Arthur] I saw them.
A woman and a man had a sledgehammer.
They destroyed the statue.
This is the first and last time
that I let anyone openly oppose me.
[ominous music playing]
Ma.
Stop worrying.
Grandpa is right. I know
how to charm Ivy. We won't lose her.
And who will handle the investigation?
Shouldn't we prioritize that?
And while you're at it, maybe, you know,
I should take her to the best spa
to relax, take her shopping…
Stop. Stop.
You'll just embarrass yourself.
She's a strong woman.
She won't get swayed by petty things.
She will respond better
to a strong man like me.
Hey, are you trying to say
that I'm weak? Is that it?
Mom, that's not what I meant.
You're the strongest woman I know.
It's just that…
Ivy's pretty much fallen for me.
It'd be easier for us
if you let me do this.
Fine. Do whatever you think is needed.
But you cannot fail. 'Cause if you do so,
then your grandpa will put
all the blame on me! Do you understand?
I understand. Don't worry.
Oh, while I'm out with Ivy,
can you please handle Natalie for me?
Fine.
[tense music playing]
Madrigal…
take the night off. I have a date.
-Thank you, Mayor.
-Sure.
[Pandoy] Mr. Fernan, we'll take care…
of the delivery.
All right. Are you sure?
-Yeah.
-Make sure you weigh them right.
I know, don't worry.
We already talked.
-Take this with you.
-Wow! That was sweet!
-Take care, okay?
-You're so sweet!
-A kiss for good luck?
-[laughing]
-Oh, you. Stop being so silly.
-Come on, Auntie. Just a peck.
Wait. That's it?
[laughing]
-Just stick close behind us, okay?
-All right.
-I'll load these on the truck.
-Stay safe, okay?
-We will.
-[Loring] All right then.
[Pandoy] No drinking, okay?
[man] All right.
-Have a safe trip.
-Take care.
-Nanny. Well…
-Yes?
-I have to go now too.
-Take this with you.
-Oh. I'll just put it here.
-Okay then.
Take care, all right?
-Thank you.
-You never know nowadays.
All right. I'll be going now.
Oh, by the way, how is your grandpa?
Do they have a suspect yet?
Not yet.
It might just be a prank.
-Go now.
-All right, Nanny.
Don't let them leave you behind.
-Take care.
-I will.
-Have some coffee.
-Thank you.
-Jepoy.
-Yes?
You have to keep an eye on Emilia
while I distract Arnaldo.
I have to know what she might be up to.
Got it.
I'm also keeping an eye
on a crazy man at the plaza.
I think he knows something.
You handle that.
[doorbell ringing]
My date is here.
Ivy.
[somber music playing]
Be careful around that man, okay?
I will.
Does Natalie know about this?
I don't want her feeling jealous.
She has nothing to be jealous of.
We aren't doing anything wrong.
Well, it depends on…
what's written
on the contract you brought.
So, tell me, Mr. Mayor.
Why did you have to take
me out on a romantic evening?
Uh… Well, to convince you.
So you won't pull
your investment on my project.
Oh, so the governor already told you.
We don't keep secrets from each other.
I don't like secrets either.
We think alike, Mr. Mayor.
So you should tell me now
if you're hiding something
about the project.
[Arnaldo] Well…
Just a minor glitch.
The land we're planning to use
is currently occupied by farmers.
But don't worry. We'll force them out.
What?
Mr. Mayor, you assured me
there wouldn't be problems.
I don't want to be involved in that.
We can't force them out.
That's illegal dispersal!
There are too many issues
for such a small project.
I'd rather invest somewhere else.
[chuckles]
Ms. Aguas, don't drop me like this.
This is why
I'm taking you out on a special date.
To convince you.
Come on, just give me a chance.
I'm all for second chances, Mr. Mayor.
Just make sure it's worthy of my time.
[tense music playing]
[Pandoy] Good evening, sir.
What's the problem?
-[cop] Get down.
-[Pandoy] Sorry?
-[Pandoy] What for?
-Get out!
-What is it, officer?
-Get out of the car!
-Get down.
-Sir… Sir. Sir.
-That hurt.
-Sir!
Be careful with those,
we still have to deliver them!
Don't destroy them!
Sir, we're going to deliver those!
Let me go! I said let me go!
[clamoring]
Sir…
[man grunting]
[Diego] Hey! Hey, that's enough!
Stop it! What do you think you're doing?
Huh? What is this?
That's enough! I said that's enough!
-What's happening?
-Ivy, stay here.
I'll see what's going on.
Diego Ardiente,
we're just following our orders.
[action music playing]
Was hurting people
part of your orders, huh?
You jerk!
Stop it! Stop!
[men grunting]
Stop!
-[gunshot]
-[cop] So you won't stop?
Stay here.
Diego! What happened here?
Ask them!
Chief, what's going on?
Put your guns down.
Put them down.
All of you, over here.
Our crops.
-Let me…
-Our harvest!
Let me do that, Mr. Pandoy.
-Mr. Pandoy, let us do that.
-[Pandoy] I'm going to help.
No. We've got this.
[tense music playing]
Stay away from us!
We don't need your help.
[Pandoy groans]
They're ruined.
You're taking the cops' side?
Didn't you see
how they hurt those farmers?
The farmers started it,
and you even joined in!
They were destroying our crops!
They were only doing their job!
Was that part of their job?
Just admit that they're abusing their
power because you're tolerating them!
That's enough!
You better show me some respect.
I'm your brother.
I'm older than you,
and above all, I'm the mayor!
[Diego] That's the problem.
You're the mayor.
You're supposed to be
defending the helpless.
But what are you doing?
-[Emilia] Hey! Enough!
-You're taking advantage of them!
-Me?
-Enough!
Why are you two fighting again?
Stop this right now!
[tense music playing]
[loud thump]
Ivy…
I'm… I'm sorry.
I didn't want this to happen.
Ivy, whatever happened…
we are really sorry about it.
It's okay.
I think I better go home now.
-Let me drive you home.
-No, no. It's fine.
I asked my driver to pick me up.
Governor.
[Raul] Where did you hear
that news, Auntie?
From someone I know at the market.
She heard from her vegetable supplier
at Ardiente
that the statue was destroyed.
Hasn't your son or your wife
called you yet?
The reception's bad here.
I rarely get a decent signal, anyway.
Actually, that's why I like it here.
Life is more peaceful.
I'm just worried…
that your absence there
might get you into trouble.
Don't worry about that.
I'll take care of it.
I'll go home tomorrow.
I'll spend the night here.
Auntie, give that to me. I'll feed her.
-Okay.
-All right.
[somber music playing]
[action music playing]
[thinking] Stop it, Jepoy.
You shouldn't want what you can't have.
-Hey. How are you?
-[man] We're okay, Mr. Diego.
Where's Nanny?
-She's right there.
-Nanny!
[crying]
Nanny, any update? How's Uncle?
He broke some bones. He might need a cast.
He's in the X-ray room.
What'll happen now?
Nanny, don't worry.
I'll take care of Uncle Pandoy.
I have some money saved.
This is too much, Diego.
Nanny,
you don't have to be ashamed.
You and Uncle Pandoy are basically family.
Let me do this for you.
[sobbing]
Thank you.
Anything for you.
Ma'am, their bills have already been paid.
-[Carlotta] What?
-Mr. Diego Ardiente-Torillo settled them.
Is that so? All right, miss. Thank you.
Sweetie, Diego has already paid the bills.
Let's go before someone sees you here.
["Sa'yo" by Silent Sanctuary playing]
[action music playing]
[tense music playing]
[heavy breathing]
[thinking] Dante? Ivy's father?
[eerie music playing]
The Ardientes will soon fall.
[evil laughing]
A rival to match them.
That woman.
The woman who destroyed the statue!
[Arthur laughing]
-Mayor?
-Madrigal.
It's so unlike you to come in this late.
I'm sorry, Mayor.
Where were you last night?
-Uh…
-Never mind.
What you do on your personal time
is none of my business.
The policemen from last night
weren't from Ardiente, right?
They don't know how things work here.
There wouldn't have been
any trouble if they didn't start it.
Make sure to sanction them.
All of them, especially
the one who fired a gun.
I don't want to hear
those farmers whine about me,
or the Ardiente family.
I'm sure their egos have grown
after what Diego did.
I've really had it with Diego.
[tense music playing]
[Ivy] Nanny Carlotta?
-Yes?
-Is everything ready?
Yes, we'll load them into the car.
Calm down, dear.
The farmers are fine now.
They'll be discharged today.
How can I calm down?
They were hurt because of me.
That's why we'll give them
a little something.
What happened wasn't your fault.
You didn't want that to happen.
This was all the Ardientes' doing.
Don't you dare blame yourself, Ivy.
Let's go now. Come on.
-All right.
-Before it gets too dark.
-I'll help.
-No, it's okay. Let's go.
-Please. Let me help.
-Bring everything to the car!
Faster!
-You don't have to--
-Let's move faster!
-[Loring] Oh, Diego…
-[sighs]
We can't thank you enough.
Nanny, just feed me a lot of
banana fritters, and I'm good.
-Okay, if that's what you want.
-[Pandoy chuckling]
-Loring, Pandoy. Diego.
-Mr. Fernan.
What's that?
Uh… Here's a little gift
from the Ardientes.
I told you they'd never let us down.
Come on, Fernan. Stop fooling yourself.
After what happened to our friends?
After what they did to them?
A little gift is enough to buy your vote?
Whatever, Loring.
It's up to you if you'll accept it or not.
Mr. Fernan, who dropped by?
Was it the mayor or the governor?
No, it was actually
the pretty Ms. Ivy Aguas.
I think she's the investor in the project.
[tense music playing]
Nanny, Uncle, I'll be right back.
But…
-I hope this helps. I'm sorry.
-Thank you.
Thank you, Ms. Ivy.
To the Ardientes as well.
We're sorry about what happened.
Some of our friends
are just really violent.
They should've listened.
They shouldn't have fought back.
There wouldn't have been any trouble.
Again, I'm sorry.
-[Diego] Ms. Aguas.
-[women] Thank you.
What are you doing here?
Um… Mr. Torillo.
Can you just leave?
Don't try to fool the farmers.
You're only after the land, right?
Mr. Torillo, I'm here
because I want to help--
You want to help?
Then leave Ardiente!
But of course, you won't do that.
Because money is more important to you
than the welfare of these farmers!
The harvest destroyed last night?
That was from the blood
and sweat of these farmers!
It's where they get the money
for their children's education!
Treatment for their sick parents!
And for their food!
And these people you're helping…
look them in the eye!
All of them will lose
their livelihood and homes!
You're smart enough to see that.
And you're beautiful too.
It's a shame you don't have a good heart.
[instrumental theme music playing]
I understand where you're
coming from, Mr. Torillo.
If you want me to leave… then I will.
I only ask you not to doubt
that I really do want to help.
Take your money when you leave too.
So the project here won't push through.
[instrumental theme music playing]
[Emilia] Arnaldo!
That brother of yours
knows nothing better
than to taint our family's name!
And where is your father?
Oh, there he is.
Raul, do you know
what your wonderful son did?
I'm sure you don't.
Because if you were home, you'd
know what's been going on here!
-Mom.
-What? It's the truth!
Where are you going now?
Raul!
[sighs]
Arnaldo, there's nothing I can do
about your father and brother anymore.
We should clean this mess up instead.
You know what? All I can think about…
is Ivy.
Now, she has more reasons
not to push through with the project.
Does your grandpa know about this yet?
-I was about to tell him.
-No. Don't tell him yet, okay?
Let's fix this ourselves. [sighs]
-I'll go talk to Ivy, okay?
-I'll talk to her, Mom.
What?
-I'll do it.
-Are you serious?
Did you forget you have lunch
with Natalie today?
-What?
-Come on, Arnaldo.
You can't push Natalie aside.
We need her for our political mission.
So focus. Okay?
Good morning, Auntie.
-Oh, Natalie, you're here.
-Hi.
Great timing.
Arnaldo's ready for your lunch.
-Great. Let's go?
-[Emilia] Go!
Let's go.
-Good morning, Mayor.
-Good morning, Chief.
-Chief.
-Gov. Good news.
We have a suspect for desecration
of the Congressman's statue.
Really?
You won't believe who this person is.
Who is it?
Uh, where's Congressman?
It'll be better if I show the report
to all three of you together.
-Okay.
-All right. Uh…
Natalie, I'm sorry,
but I have to deal with this first.
Uh, okay. Um, I understand.
I'll make it up to you.
Madrigal, please escort Natalie.
-Bye.
-Let's go, Chief.
-Chief. Let's go.
-All right.
Nanny, I feel I need to do something.
I have to make it up to them.
I can talk to Emilia.
Maybe I should ask her to build
the project on a different lot,
so the farmers can keep their land.
What if she refuses?
If she does…
then I'll pull out of my investment.
Ivy, is that even possible?
You might anger the Ardientes.
Anger them? The Ardientes
can't get mad at me.
I can tear them down.
I can expose their lies.
[Jepoy] Ivy, hold it.
Before you do that,
you need to know something.
What is it?
Someone saw you destroying the statue.
What?! Who saw me?
His name is Arthur. He's nuts.
Don't worry, no one will believe him.
Arthur? Nuts?
Arthur?
His name sounds familiar.
[Camia] Come on, hon.
Your co-workers did say
Arthur has a mental condition.
Arthur…
My father used to have
a co-worker with that name.
Exactly.
It's him?
I found these in his house.
These are my father's files.
Why does Arthur have them?
I've been wondering that too.
Aside from that, I saw
some dynamite in his house.
Seems like he's plotting
something against the Ardientes.
Arthur was Dad's co-worker.
It's possible he knew something
about Dad's plans against the Ardientes.
And when Dad died, he took all his files…
to accomplish my father's plans.
Jepoy, here's what you should do.
Before the Ardientes
discover Arthur's plan,
you need to take him away from here.
[action music playing]
[Julio] Where did you get these?
My men followed him, Congressman.
Those pictures were taken near his house.
You mean this lunatic
is the one going against us?
So, where is this man now?
He's been detained, Congressman.
Oh, I see.
[Julio] So…
-Can you bring him here?
-Of course, sir.
And one more thing.
Could you tell your men…
to burn all the documents, and pictures…
that they find in his house?
-Yes, sir.
-Thank you.
No problem, sir.
[grunting]
[tense music playing]
I thought you already got rid of that man.
Didn't he work as a clerk
in the public lawyer's office?
He must know something about us, then.
And about what you did to Atty. Cruz.
Of course, Papa.
But as far as I'm concerned…
Atty. Cruz died of heart attack
while driving.
Besides, we shouldn't
waste our time on this man.
He just wanders around town,
but he will do us no harm, Papa.
You know what?
We should just send him
to a mental institution.
Hold on. I'll call the doctor.
-[tense music playing]
-Ouch!
You better be thankful that's all I did.
It's your fault for not using your head.
Do you really think a nutjob like him…
is capable of doing all this alone, huh?
Grandpa…
you mean he's got an accomplice?
Definitely.
-Let me handle him, Papa.
-No.
Stop it.
I don't want you
to be involved in any of this anymore.
Emilia, you disappoint me.
You…
and your worthless husband…
really deserve each other.
Arnaldo's the only one I can rely on.
Get out of my face. Go! Now!
No!
[tense music playing]
Arthur? Arthur?
Arthur?
[eerie music playing]
[action music playing]
[cop 1] The Chief said to burn all papers.
[cop 2] Okay, sir.
Let's do this.
All right.
Well, I'm sure you've calmed down
after taking a bath.
Everyone's talking about
what you said to Ms. Ivy.
Nanny, I only told her
the things she had to hear.
I understand, Diego.
But what you did was--
But Nanny…
I couldn't control myself.
I think it's better
if she just leaves this place.
Do you think she'll listen to you?
What will you do if she doesn't?
How about this? Why don't you…
you know… talk to Ms. Ivy?
Do it now.
[sniffing]
While you are fresh from the shower
and smelling so good!
I'm sure she'll give in!
Nanny, was that another one of your jokes?
[laughs] No, I meant that!
[Loring laughs] See, you're laughing now!
Just try it.
There's nothing a good talk can't fix.
[pensive music playing]
I think the Ardientes
got their hands on Arthur first.
What do they plan to do with him?
He's mentally incapacitated!
Nanny…
The Ardientes are ruthless.
They won't hesitate to take down
anyone who gets in their way.
Jepoy.
We have to save Arthur.
Leave it to me.
[Ivy] No.
-I'm coming with you.
-What?
[action music playing]
Grandpa, we have him.
You know what to do.
Don't delay it.
Put an end to this.
Yes, Grandpa.
[tense music playing]
[doorbell ringing]
-Are we expecting anyone?
-No one.
Who could it be?
Diego?
[crickets chirping]
[engine running]
[somber music playing]
-Mom?
-Diego.
What are you doing here?
Now Emilia too? What are they doing here?
I have to go, Ivy.
Entertain them first.
I swear, I'll save Arthur.
Be careful.
[tense music playing]
What are you doing here?
I wanted to talk to Ms. Aguas.
About the export processing zone.
Diego, don't stick your nose
where it doesn't belong.
-But Mom…
-Leave.
Leave now, Diego.
Mom.
I said leave.
[door opening]
Governor?
[Emilia] Ivy.
-Go on, son.
-Mister…
[Emilia] You may go now.
I'll call you once I'm done.
Mr. Torillo?
-[Emilia] No, no, no.
-Why--
[Emilia] It's nothing. Um…
He just asked me something.
Go now. You take care, okay?
Let's go?
Oh. Okay.
-Here. I brought wine.
-Come in.
[tense music playing]
[ominous music playing]
-[Arnaldo grunts]
-[Arthur screaming]
[whipping]
-[whipping]
-[screaming and grunting]
You murderer!
You demon!
Your soul will burn in hell!
-[Arthur groans]
-You know what…
I'm only wasting my time on you because…
I want to personally hear you
spill the information I need.
But don't worry.
I'll send you
to hell once I'm done with you.
Why?
What are you going to do to me?!
-What will you do to me?
-It depends.
It all depends on your answer.
[Arthur whimpering]
Because I don't believe that
you did this all on your own.
And I don't believe you're crazy.
I know you're just pretending.
So, you should tell me…
whom your boss is. Who ordered you?
[ominous music playing]
[laughing]
[cries] I don't know anything.
I don't know anything.
I don't know anything!
Who ordered you?
[action music playing]
[whimpering]
I'll talk!
I'll talk! I'll talk! I'll talk!
So, what brings you here?
I came here to celebrate with my friend.
Celebrate? What?
[chuckles] Didn't you hear?
About what?
We arrested the culprit who
destroyed my father's statue.
You did? Please sit down.
Yes!
And it turns out the man
was full-on crazy.
Crazy? Was this all a prank?
So, where is he?
In a psychiatric hospital?
I don't know.
But one thing's for sure.
He'll pay for what he did.
[sighs deeply]
I have a feeling that tonight
is going to be my lucky night!
You know why?
Lots of good things
are happening to our family.
First, the suspect who destroyed
the statue was caught.
And tonight, you're going
to sign this contract, Ivy.
[tense music playing]
[chuckles]
Governor, don't be in a rush.
Maybe we should take
a sip of your wine first.
And if I like it,
then I might be convinced
to sign that contract.
I don't need wine for that.
Are you sure?
Didn't Arnaldo tell you that
I'm not easy to please?
Try me.
Good.
[labored breathing]
Now spill.
The savior has arrived
to bring you to your knees!
-[laughing]
-[screams, whips]
-[Arnaldo screaming]
No one messes with my grandfather!
[laughing]
-[Arnaldo screams, whips]
-[Arthur grunts, laughs]
[screams, whips, laughing]
I grew up with my grandfather
being respected!
People fear him, and you have
the guts to mock him?
[Arnaldo screams, whips]
[Arthur groans]
As long as I'm alive…
no one can hurt my grandfather.
-No one!
-[grunts]
[tense music playing]
[labored breathing]
[Emilia] So, how do you like the wine?
It's okay, it's sweet.
But…
it's too light.
In terms of a person…
it's as ineffective…
as a bootlicker.
[sighs]
On the contrary,
this is how I like my wine to be.
Sweet.
But has quite the kick?
It's more like me.
Should I be nervous?
Ivy, what's important
is we understand each other.
So, why don't you sign
our deal, the contract right there,
so we both live happily ever after?
[laughs]
[somber music playing]
I don't live in fairy tales…
nor do I believe in happily-ever-afters.
I live in what's real…
and where I'm sure I'm safe.
[laughing]
Ivy, how can I protect you
if you're going against me?
What? Against you?
Governor, we're friends!
Didn't I save your life?
I know, that's why I trust you.
I know you won't push me
to do something I'll regret in the end.
[tense music playing]
-[sighs]
-Arnaldo.
What is it, Diego?
I want to talk to you and Grandpa.
I'm busy, Diego. Maybe tomorrow.
If you won't talk to me,
I'll go straight to Grandpa.
You have the same opinions
and decisions anyway.
If this is about the export
processing zone again,
you're just wasting your breath.
It's better than not using it.
-See you.
-Arnaldo
[tense music playing]
Whatever it is you're up to…
I hope you think it over.
Who are you to give me advice?
I'm the mayor. And you?
I'm the Ardiente who cares
about the people.
[Emilia] So, Ivy, what do you have to say?
Is it a yes or yes?
I want to say yes, but…
like what I said,
my lawyers have to look it over.
[sighs]
You know, Ivy… from the looks of it…
you're giving me a hard time.
You are making me beg,
and I'm not liking it.
To be honest, if the congressman
was the one who asked me,
I might say yes to him.
But I am the governor!
And the governor
is as powerful as the congressman!
You're only a governor in name.
I can see how you let your father
and even your son boss you around.
It's like you just go to the
office to sign, give orders--
Shut up! You don't know
what you're talking about!
Of course I know what I'm saying!
If you say you're good
at persuading people, well,
I'm good at reading them.
And I can read you like a book,
Governor Emilia.
From head to toe.
[sighs]
[somber piano music playing]
Impressive!
[laughing]
You just impressed me, Miss Aguas.
For the first time…
I met another woman as powerful as me.
Someone who is straightforward,
doesn't suck up to me,
and only tells the truth,
which is what I really like.
[tense music playing]
Diego…
Let's not tire each other out.
The project will push through.
And that is final.
Grandpa.
Is there any way to change your mind?
You've disappointed me enough, Diego.
I have given up all hope…
that you have anything good
to offer our family.
Thank you for your time.
But the truth is…
I knew you were going to say these things.
I only wanted to see
if I'd be able to change your mind.
Grandpa…
you have so many loyalists
who support and believe in you.
I thought that maybe they see
something in you that I don't.
What could they see in you?
Because no matter
how I look at it, I see nothing.
I don't see anything.
So…
Grandpa, we're even.
Because if I disappointed
you, you disappointed me too.
But…
But, Grandpa, I hope
that one day, you can change.
[tense music playing]
You know… you just earned my respect.
[scoffs]
Governor, don't get me wrong.
I didn't say that to belittle you.
The truth is I want you
to be brave as a woman.
Someone who can fight back and win.
-But I can win if I want to.
-Exactly!
Exactly, Governor,
but it's difficult, isn't it?
I know it is.
I know the hardships
a woman faces in this world
governed by men.
I went through those things
doing business.
And I succeeded.
So, Governor, I want you to succeed too.
Because you live in a world
surrounded by powerful men.
It's tough because they're your family.
But I know.
I know you can keep up with them.
I guess that's the curse on us women, huh?
Especially on me.
It's my family.
Papa, my husband, my son…
They are all domineering.
I only wanted for my father
to cheer for my success
and not see the failure in me.
I only want him to tell me…
"I'm proud of you."
But Papa…
My father's heart is as hard as steel.
But even steel can melt.
[tense music playing]
And you need to stand your ground.
Maybe it's time you show them
that you can stand beside them.
Not as a woman,
but as their equal.
As Governor Emilia, and as an Ardiente.
You're more than capable.
[Julio] You're a governor!
You have no self-respect!
[Emilia] You are right! I am the governor,
and I can do anything I want!
[Ivy] Because tomorrow,
the Ardientes will wake up
-to a living nightmare.
-The congressman's share!
-Is this all of it?
-Give it to him.
Is it true you're a gambling operator
and protector?
[Ivy] If the issue spreads,
the media will swarm you,
especially because you passed
the Anti-Gambling Bill.
If I were you, I'd distance myself
from the congressman.
You moron! This is all your fault!
-[Raul] I'll kill you!
-Raul, stop!
[theme music playing]